encashit.com 2015-08-12

# Privacy Policy - Encashit.com

* * *

1.PRIVACY STATEMENT

Encashit has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website Encashit.

2.GATHERING OF SYSTEM INFORMATION

When you use Encashit's services we track your activity on our website. Your personal information is used to identify you in our system, allowing Encashit to contact you about the status of your order or respond to your questions via e-mail or telephone, and to allow you to store your basic information for repeat checkouts. We also use the information gathered from tracking user activities to improve our service. We also track your Internet Protocol (IP) address, domain name (if applicable), browser type, session duration, and transaction data, which is available to any site to which you connect. Encashit uses this information to administer the site and to further improve our service to you.

3.TRACKING OF COOKIES

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies from Encashit do not damage your computer. We use cookies to save your password, so you don't have to enter your password on every page.

4\. CUSTOMER IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Our site's registration form requires users to give us in depth contact information. This information is used to help us serve you better. It is never shared with third parties, except when you specifically authorize us. Your contact information is also used by our staff to contact you when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products only, and we do not share this information with our partners, unless you explicitly authorize us to.

5.INTERNAL USE OF INFORMATION

Our site provides a mechanism for people to send feedback and request more information. This information is not uniquely stored, but may be aggregated with other data to insure that we properly meet users' expectations and have the necessary resources planned to accommodate future growth. A user's contact information is also used to get in touch with the user when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the customer for products at the time of checkout, and for this purpose only, through our secure payment gateway.

6\. UPDATE POLICY

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

Log in to your account with the account login link on our website. Upon entering your registered email and password, you are free to edit or remove your information at any time.

If you have trouble editing or removing your details for any reason, simply contact us with your change request through the Contact Us form on our website.

7\. CONTACTING Encashit

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Encashit, you can contact by emailing us at support@encashit.com
